{
    "subject": "resource/Mary_Neal",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:1860_births",
    "human_readable": "Mary Neal's subject is Category:1860_births.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8307152390480042,
            "question": "What category does Mary Neal's birth belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.678510844707489,
            "question": "In what year was Mary Neal born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5574718117713928,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about notable events that occurred in the year of Mary Neal's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45470738410949707,
            "question": "Who else was born in the same year as Mary Neal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4415661692619324,
            "question": "Can you provide examples of influential figures who were also born in 1860?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4301460385322571,
            "question": "What are some commonalities among individuals born in the year 1860?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34083184599876404,
            "question": "What historical events might have shaped the lives of those born in 1860?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3054831027984619,
            "question": "How did life differ for people born in 1860 compared to today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17980696260929108,
            "question": "What were some significant cultural or technological advancements during the year 1860?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14445582032203674,
            "question": "Were there any major political changes happening globally in 1860?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Mary Neal's subject is Category:1860_births.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1303_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were some significant cultural or technological advancements during the year 1860?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1303_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did life differ for people born in 1860 compared to today?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1303_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What historical events might have shaped the lives of those born in 1860?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1303_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1303_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1303_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1303_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1303_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1303_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1303_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1303_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1303_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1303_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1303_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents contain information about Mary Neal, including her birthdate (1860) and a statement that she was born in Edgbaston, England. This supports the triple that Mary Neal's subject is Category:1860_births."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Mary Neal, including her birth year of 1860. Therefore, the statement that \"Mary Neal's subject is Category:1860_births\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Mary Neal was born in 1860 but the given context does not provide any information about her birth year, hence it cannot be accurately determined that she falls under Category:1860_births.",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}